{"data":{"site":{"pathPrefix":"/restaurant-inspections"},"postgres":{"establishment":[{"establishmentid":"51623109","name":"Ice Cream & Cafe La Niña","address":"7431 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209","owner":"Rocio Karina Rocha","licenseNumber":"246045","licenseType":"Fixed Establishment","establishmentType":"Food Service Establishment","establishmentStatus":"Open","riskCategory":"High","reviewFrequencyDays":"180","coords":"-83.12244,42.31304","geojson":{"id":"51623109","type":"Feature","geometry":{"type":"Point","coordinates":[-83.122442329,42.313037445]},"properties":{"name":"Ice Cream & Cafe La Niña","owner":"Rocio Karina Rocha","address":"7431 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209","license_type":"Fixed Establishment","risk_category":"High","license_number":"246045","establishmentid":"51623109","establishment_type":"Food Service Establishment","establishment_status":"Open","review_frequency_days":"180","most_recent_license_date":"10/11/2019"}},"nearbyList":[{"establishmentid":"201","name":"Taqueria El Nacimiento","address":"7400 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4358","name":"Domino's Pizza","address":"7603 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1342","name":"Restaurant Nuestra Familia","address":"7620 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1494","name":"J & J Coney Island #3","address":"7220 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"279","name":"Pauls Pizzeria","address":"7635 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"1523","name":"Latin American Social Ed. Development","address":"7150 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"995","name":"Harms School Elementary","address":"2400 Central Ave","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"454","name":"Taqueria Los Altos","address":"7056 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"3858","name":"Pollos Los Gallos","address":"7135 Dix Ave","zipcode":"48209"},{"establishmentid":"4792","name":"Las Palmas Neveria Y Cafeteria","address":"7009 W Vernor","zipcode":"48209"}],"inspectionsByEstablishmentidList":[{"inspectionid":"49731","inspectionDate":"2019-11-05T00:00:00","inspectionType":"Routine Inspection","inCompliance":"Yes","violationsByInspectionidList":[{"violationCode":"MFL289.6149","violationDescription":"Definitions; satisfaction of  section 3-603.11 of food code; statement; disclosures and reminders; text;  exemptions.*  Sec. 6149. (1) As used in this section: (P)    (a) &quot; Publicly available&quot; means  accessible to consumers, without their having to request it, before their  placing food orders or making their selections.    (b) &quot; Selection information&quot; means  whatever consumers read to make their order selections, such as menu, table  tent, placard, chalkboard, or other written means.    (2) To satisfy section 3-603.11 of the food code, the food establishment may  provide the following statement on selection information so that it is publicly  available: &quot; Ask your server about menu items that are cooked to order or  served raw. Consuming raw or undercooked meats, poultry, seafood, shellfish, or  eggs may increase your risk of foodborne illness&quot;.(P)    (4) The language for the menu items shall match the language used for the  disclosure and the reminder.  The  disclosure and reminder may also be in additional languages.(P)    (5) The text for disclosures and reminders shall meet the following requirements: (P)    (a) The text size for statements on handheld  menus or table tents shall be visually equivalent to at least 11-point font  size or may be visually equivalent to the font size of menu item descriptions.    (b) Text color provides a clear contrast to  background.    (6) Table tents, placards, or chalkboards that are used exclusively to list food  items that are offered as daily, weekly, or temporary specials are exempt from  the requirements of this section when those food items also appear in the  primary selection information that contains the disclosures and reminders  meeting the requirements of this section.(S)","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":null,"subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Menu","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-702.11","violationDescription":"UTENSILS and FOOD-CONTACT SURFACES of EQUIPMENT shall be SANITIZED before use after cleaning. (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Clean utensil(s) and food-contact surface(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not sanitized","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"SANITIZING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Equipment/utensils must be sanitized after cleaning."},{"violationCode":"3-302.11","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD shall be protected from cross contamination by:  \r\n(1) Except as specified in (1)(c) below, separating raw animal FOODS during         storage, preparation, holding, and display from:\r\n(a) Raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD including other raw animal FOOD such as FISH for sushi or MOLLUSCAN SHELLFISH, or other raw READY-TO-EAT FOOD such as fruits and vegetables,(P) and\r\n(b) Cooked READY-TO-EAT FOOD; (P)\r\n(c) Frozen, commercially processed and packaged raw animal FOOD may be          stored or displayed with or above frozen, commercially processed and           packaged, ready-to-eat food.\r\n(2) Except when combined as ingredients, separating types of raw animal FOODS    from each other such as beef, FISH, lamb, pork, and POULTRY during storage,        preparation, holding, and display by:\r\n(a) Using separate EQUIPMENT for each type, (P) or\r\n(b) Arranging each type of FOOD in EQUIPMENT so that cross contamination of one type with another is prevented, (P) and\r\n(c) Preparing each type of FOOD at different times or in separate areas; (P)\r\n","violationType":"Priority","itemDescription":"Raw animal food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored over/next to","subProblem":"Ready-to-eat food(s)","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"RAW FOOD STORAGE","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Store raw animal foods below and away from foods needing little or no further prep."},{"violationCode":"6-302.11","violationDescription":"A supply of toilet tissue shall be available at each toilet.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Toilet paper","subItem":"at toilet in restroom","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"Toilet paper","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"6-301.12","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with:\r\n(A) Individual, disposable towels; (Pf)\r\n(B) A continuous towel system that supplies the user with a clean towel;(Pf) or \r\n(C) A heated-air hand drying device.(Pf)\r\n(D) A hand drying device that employs an air-knife system that delivers high velocity pressurized air at ambient temperatures.(Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitary hand drying provisions","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"RESTROOM(S)","subLocation":"Hand-drying towels","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"6-301.11","violationDescription":"Each HANDWASHING SINK or group of 2 adjacent HANDWASHING SINKS shall be provided with a supply of hand cleaning liquid, powder, or bar soap. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Soap","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Handwashing soap","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"3-501.17","violationDescription":"(A)  READY-TO-EAT, POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  prepared and held refrigerated for more than 24 hours in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT  shall be clearly marked at the time of preparation to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n(B)  A container of refrigerated, commercially prepared READY-TO-EAT POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD (TIME/TEMPERATURE CONTROL FOR SAFETY FOOD)  shall be clearly marked, at the time the original container is opened in a FOOD ESTABLISHMENT, to indicate the date or day by which the FOOD shall be consumed. (Pf)\r\n\r\nA date marking system that does not exceed 7 days, including date of preparation, or opening is to be used. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"In house prepared ready-to-eat potentially hazardous  food(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Without date of consumption marking","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"DATE MARKING","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Datemark with a discard date of 7 days or less."},{"violationCode":"4-302.14","violationDescription":"A test kit or other device that accurately measures the concentration in mg/L of SANITIZING solutions shall be provided. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Sanitizer test kit","subItem":"chlorine","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"3 COMPARTMENT SINK AREA","subLocation":"Test strips","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-302.12","violationDescription":"(A) FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be provided and readily accessible for use in ensuring attainment and maintenance of FOOD temperatures as specified under Chapter 3. (Pf)   \r\n(B) A TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE with a suitable small-diameter probe that is designed to measure the temperature of thin masses shall be provided and readily accessible to accurately measure the temperature in thin FOODS such as MEAT patties and FISH filets. (Pf)\r\n","violationType":"Foundation","itemDescription":"Food thermometer(s)","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Food thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"MFL289.2129","violationDescription":"Sec. 2129. (1) All food establishments shall employ a minimum of 1 managerial employee as a food safety manager, who must be an individual who is currently certified under a personnel certification program accredited by the American National Standards Institute, utilizing the Conference for Food Protection standards:\r\n(2) Beginning January 14, 2017 and every 5 years thereafter, a certified  food safety manager who supervises the operations of a food service establishment shall have completed a food safety training program\r\ncontaining an allergen awareness  component that has been approved by  the department. A food service establishment shall retain records on the  site of the food service establishment documenting compliance of its  certified food safety managers with this subsection. ","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Person-in-charge","subItem":"","problemDescription":null,"subProblem":"","location":"ESTABLISHMENT","subLocation":"Certified Manager","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":null},{"violationCode":"6-301.14","violationDescription":"A sign or poster that notifies FOOD EMPLOYEES to wash their hands shall be provided at all HANDWASHING SINKS used by FOOD EMPLOYEES and shall be clearly visible to FOOD EMPLOYEES.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Handwashing signage","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"At hand sink","location":"HANDSINK(S)","subLocation":"Hand washing signage","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide"},{"violationCode":"4-204.112","violationDescription":"(A)  In a mechanically refrigerated or hot FOOD storage unit, the sensor of a TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE shall be located to measure the air temperature in the warmest part of a mechanically refrigerated unit and in the coolest part of a hot FOOD storage unit.\r\n(B)  Cold or hot holding EQUIPMENT used for POTENTIALLY HAZARDOUS FOOD shall be designed to include and shall be equipped with at least one integral or permanently affixed TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICE that is located to allow easy viewing of the device's temperature display (EXCEPT, heat lamps, cold plates, steam tables, or other equipment where it is not practical).\r\n(C)  TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES shall be designed to be easily readable.\r\n(D)  FOOD TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES and water TEMPERATURE MEASURING DEVICES on WAREWASHING machines shall have a numerical scale, printed record, or digital readout in increments no greater than 1C or 2F in the intended range of use. (Pf)\r\n\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Thermometer(s)","subItem":"refrigeration","problemDescription":"Not provided","subProblem":"","location":"COOLER","subLocation":"Thermometer(s)","corrected":"Yes","daysToCorrect":"10","correctedDate":"2019-12-03T00:00:00","correctionDescription":"Provide."},{"violationCode":"4-401.11","violationDescription":"EQUIPMENT, a cabinet used for the storage of FOOD, or a cabinet that is used to store cleaned and SANITIZED EQUIPMENT, UTENSILS, laundered LINENS, and SINGLE-SERVICE and SINGLE-USE ARTICLES may not be located in an unsuitable areas or where exposed to possible contamination.\r\n","violationType":"Core","itemDescription":"Equipment","subItem":"","problemDescription":"Stored","subProblem":"In mechanical room","location":"MECHANICAL ROOM","subLocation":"Equipment","corrected":"Not required","daysToCorrect":"30","correctedDate":null,"correctionDescription":"Remove and store in protected area."}]}]}],"maxInspectionDate":[{"inspectionDate":"2020-10-30T00:00:00"}]}},"pageContext":{"eid":"51623109"}}